Guide to the Steichen Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Steichen family papers
1984-2014
YCAL MSS 1080
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
41.75
(43 boxes)
The Steichen family papers consist of photographs, correspondence, writings, exhibition materials, legal papers, genealogical materials, audiovisual materials, digital media, and other papers relating to Edward J. Steichen and members of his family, including his wives Clara Smith Steichen, Dana Steichen, and Joanna T. Steichen, his daughters Mary Steichen Calderone and Charlotte "Kate" Rodina Steichen, his granddaughters Linda and Nell Martin and Francesca and Maria Calderone-Steichen, and his sister Lilian "Paula" Steichen and her husband, poet Carl Sandburg. Photographs and photograph albums by Edward Steichen and other photographers include portraits of Edward Steichen and other family members, photographs of family homes, and other subjects. Correspondence includes family correspondence with Carl Sandburg, and correspondence with playwright Edward Albee and others. Writings include works by family members, including Joanna T. Steichen and Francesca Steichen Calderone, as well as writings of others about Edward Steichen and Mary Calderone Steichen. Exhibition materials document exhibitions created by or relating to Edward Steichen. Legal papers include both estate papers and documentation of a lawsuit with the Museum of Modern Art regarding the disputed ownership of ''Vue de Collioure a l'Eglise,'' a painting by Matisse lent by Charlotte "Kate" Rodina Steichen and the subsequent sale of the painting by the Steichen family. Audiovisual materials include oral histories and documentaries about Edward Steichen.
Steichen Family
Steichen, Edward, 1879-1973
Arrangement
Organized into three groupings: February 2014 Acquisition; 5 June 2014 Acquisition; and 25 June 2014 Acquisition.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 26, 27 (audiovisual materials): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 28, 39 (digital media): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Francesca Calderone-Steichen, 2014.
Edward J. Steichen
Edward J. Steichen (1879-1973) was a photographer and painter, as well as an art gallery and museum curator. Born in Luxembourg, he emigrated to the United States in 1881. Steichen was married three times. His first marriage, to Clara Smith Steichen (1875-1952), ended in divorce in 1922. His second marriage, to Dana Steichen, spanned from 1923 to her death in 1957. Steichen's third marriage, to Joanna T. Steichen, began in 1960 and lasted until his death.
Mary Steichen Calderone
Mary Steichen Calderone (1904-1998), daughter of photographer and artist Edward J. Steichen and Clara Smith Steichen, was a physician and a public health advocate for sex education. She had four daughters: Linda Martin and Nell Martin with her first husband, W. Lon Martin, and Francesca Calderone-Steichen and Maria Calderone-Steichen with her second husband, Frank Calderone.
Charlotte "Kate" Rodina Steichen
Charlotte "Kate" Rodina Steichen (1908-1988), daughter of photographer and artist Edward J. Steichen and Clara Smith Steichen, was an administrative assistant from 1950 to 1960 to the editor in chief at the Doubleday Publishing Company, Kenneth Dale McCormick.
Lilian "Paula" Steichen
Lilian "Paula" Steichen (1883-1977) was the sister of photographer and artist Edward J. Steichen and wife of poet Carl Sandburg.
Scope and Contents
The Steichen family papers consist of photographs, correspondence, writings, exhibition materials, legal papers, genealogical materials, audiovisual materials, digital media, and other papers relating to Edward J. Steichen and members of his family, including his wives Clara Smith Steichen, Dana Steichen, and Joanna T. Steichen, his daughters Mary Steichen Calderone and Charlotte "Kate" Rodina Steichen, his granddaughters Linda and Nell Martin and Francesca and Maria Calderone-Steichen, and his sister Lilian "Paula" Steichen and her husband, poet Carl Sandburg. Photographs and photograph albums by Edward Steichen and other photographers include portraits of Edward Steichen and other family members, photographs of family homes, and other subjects. Correspondence includes family correspondence with Carl Sandburg, and correspondence with playwright Edward Albee and others. Writings include works by family members, including Joanna T. Steichen and Francesca Steichen-Calderone, as well as writings of others about Edward Steichen and Mary Calderone Steichen. Exhibition materials document exhibitions created by or relating to Edward Steichen. Legal papers include both estate papers and documentation of a lawsuit with the Museum of Modern Art regarding the disputed ownership of ''Vue de Collioure a l'Eglise,'' a painting by Matisse lent by Charlotte "Kate" Rodina Steichen and the subsequent sale of the painting by the Steichen family. Audiovisual materials include oral histories and documentaries about Edward Steichen.
Photographers -- United States; Audiovisual materials; Born digital; Photograph albums; Photographic prints; Photographers -- United States -- 20th Century; Albee, Edward, 1928-2016; Calderone, Mary Steichen, 1904-1998; Calderone-Steichen, Francesca; Calderone-Steichen, Maria; Sandburg, Carl, 1878-1967; Steichen Family; Steichen, Charlotte Rodina, 1908-1988; Steichen, Dana, 1894-1957; Steichen, Clara Smith, 1875-1952; Steichen, Edward, 1879-1973; Steichen, Joanna T.; Steichen, Lilian, 1883-1977
- February 2014 Acquisition, 1896-2010; 25.67; (28 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Arranged in roughly the order in which the materials were received.
  - Photographs, 1914-1938; 2 folders (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes one snapshot of Mary Steichen Calderone, her father, aunt, and uncle in the snow, Christmas Day 1914; two photographs taken at Voulangis, one including the elderly Edward Steichen; and one negative of Mary Steichen Calderone in 1938 when she was Mary Steichen Martin, and her daughter Lydia by her first husband.
  - Correspondence, 1933-1989; 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Articles, 1957-1988 (Box 1)
    Includes various magazines, journals and brochures related to Edward Steichen and his work.
  - Genealogy, 1954-1983; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Photograph album, 1959 (Box 1)
    A green album of photographs of Edward J. Steichen, compiled by his third wife, Joanna Tuab Steichen.
  - Legal documents, 1894-1946 (Box 1)
    Includes the following:
    "Old Legal Documents: passports etc." for Edward Steichen
    Certificate of completion of courses in elementary school and subsequent eligibility for high school, Public Schools of Milwaukee, July 3, 1894 [6th District School]
    Certificate of Naturalization, Milwaukee County, USA, March 27, 1900. Signed Eduard J.
    Passport: March 29, 1900 [signed Eduard J. Steichen]. Large parchment sheet, good for two years. Description: Age 21; Height 5 feet 11 1/2 inches; high forehead; blue eyes; Roman nose; normal mouth; round chin; brown hair; Fair complexion; round, full face.
    Passport: March 13, 1920 [signed Edward J. Steichen] Description: Age 40 years; height 6 feet 1 inch; forehead broad; eyes blue gray; Hair straight; mouth straight; chin round; hair dark; complexion: medium; face oval; distinguishing marks: birth mark over eye; date of birth: March 27, 2879; occupation: artist. #185281.
    Xeroxed copy, Notice of Separation from the US Naval Service, Feb 26, 1942
  - Divorce papers, 1922-1933 (Box 1)
    Includes Edward Steichen - Clara Smith Steichen French divorce papers, carbon copy, and related correspondence.
  - Correspondence, 1932-1959 (Box 1)
    Includes correspondence to and from Edward Steichen, including one handwritten letter from his mother, Marie Kemp Steichen.
  - Exhibition photographs, 1994; 2 folders (Box 1)
    Includes exhibition information and photographs from "Within the Family: Private and Professional Photography by Edward Steichen," March 6-April 17, 1994, The Gallery at Briston-Myers Squibb, Princeton, NJ.
  - Original box description (Box 2)
  - "Edward J. Steichen: A Documentary", undated (Box 2)
    Includes a bound text: "Edward J. Steichen: A Documentary" by Claude Waringo
  - "Help Me Find My Boy!", 1932 (Box 2)
    Includes a Travelers Aid Society public service brochure: "Help Me Find My Boy!" with photographs by Edward Steichen.
  - Publications, 1937-1955; 2 folders (Box 2)
    Magazines, Journals, Clippings, Brochures and Programs featuring Edward Steichen
  - Catalogues and journals, 1966-1999; 2 folders (Box 2)
    Includes magazines, journals, clippings, brochures, and programs featuring Edward Steichen.
  - Articles on and by Steichen, 1944-1997; 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Redding, CT, property papers, 1966-1977; 3 folders (Box 2)
    Includes records regarding the disposition of Steichen's property in Redding, CT.
  - Edward Steichen's 90th birthday party, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Funeral plans, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Original box description (Box 3)
  - Ron Gedrim thesis on Steichen and Flowers, 1990-1993; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Transcripts of Joanna Steichen on Edward Steichen, 1982-1997 (Box 3)
  - "Family of Man" media, 1991-1994; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Thesis by Dider Damiani, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Chronology, undated (Box 3)
    Includes Grace Mayer's chronology. Grace Mayer was Steichen's assistant at the Museum of Modern Art for many years.
  - Correspondence, 1973-1987; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Mary Steichen Calderone biographical data and photograph, 1988 (Box 4)
  - "The First Picture Book: Everyday Things for Babies", undated (Box 4)
  - Hecksher Museum exhibition, 1951-1985 (Box 4)
    Inlcudes Mary Steichen Calderone's file on Edward Steichen's Hecksher Museum exhibition, including a list of Steichen paintings she loaned to the museum.
  - "From Then Till Now", 1934 (Box 4)
    Includes "From Then Till Now," by James Barnes, an account of WWI involving Edward Steichen.
  - Voulangis photographs, undated (Box 4)
    Includes photographs of Voulangis, France [Mary Steichen Calderone's childhood home in the French countryside].
  - Testimony to International Organizations Employees Loyalty Board, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Mary Steichen Calderone correspondence, articles, and fragments of biographical writing, 1982-1989 (Box 4)
  - "Will and Codicil", 1988-1992 (Box 4)
  - Poems, undated (Box 4)
    Includes a torn black binder with poems by others. Inscribed on inside cover, "Mary Steichen Martin, Harmon, NY, Valuable, reward if returned to owner."
  - "Book", undated (Box 4)
    Yellow folder entitled "Book" containing excerpts by Francesca Calderone-Steichen.
  - "Let Us Celebrater Her Life", 1999 (Box 4)
    Includes a white notebook, "Let us Celebrate Her Life," Memorial Tribute to Mary Steichen Calderone, October 27, 1999.
  - "In Memoriam: Dr. Mary Steichen Calderone 1904-1998", 1998-1999 (Box 4)
  - Material sent to Mary Steichen Calderone by SIECUS, 1982-2004 (Box 4)
  - Interview, 1974 (Box 4)
    Includes a copy of an interview with Mary Steichen Calderone for the Schlesinger-Rockefeller Oral History Project, August 7, 1974
  - Writings, 1983-1989; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Personal and family, 1941-2010; 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1998-2000 (Box 4)
  - List of wishes from Umpawaug, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Rodin, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Estate of Edward Steichen, 1964-1990 (Box 4)
  - Brearly Bulletin, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Vassar College medal, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Original box description (Box 5)
  - Family history, 1976-2001 (Box 5)
  - Keets family history, 2001-2003 (Box 5)
  - "An Ozark Childhood", undated (Box 5)
  - "Repatriating Clara's Ashes", 2001 (Box 5)
    Francesca Calderone-Steichen's manuscript about her grandmother Clara.
  - Scrapbook, 1914-1933 (Box 5)
  - Photographs, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, 1903-1982; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Correspondence about Clara, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, photographs, correspondence, 1916-2001 (Box 5)
  - Legal documents and correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 5)
  - "Intimate Respect" draft, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Francesca Calderone-Steichen correspondence, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Songs by Clara Smith Steichen and Augusta Holmes; lyrics and music, undated (Box 6)
  - Original box description (Box 7)
  - Sandburg correspondence, 1949-1961 (Box 7)
    Includes copies of Edward and Dana Steichen's correspondence with Carl and Paula Sandburg and family.
  - "Steichen, Dana, Unknown. Umpawaug, before house was built," photograph, undated (Box 7)
  - Francesca correspondence, 1954 (Box 7)
    Letter from Francesca Calderone-Steichen to her sister Maria Calderone-Steichen, May 29, 1954, describing a visit to their grandfather, "Bumpa," aka Edward Steichen and their step-grandmother, Dana Steichen.
  - Book contract, 1959 (Box 7)
  - "Dana Glover Steichen (manuscript)", undated (Box 7)
  - "Dana Glover Steichen," copies of articles, 1916-1973 (Box 7)
  - "Sandburg Poems Given to Dana", undated (Box 7)
  - "E-mail Remembrance of Dana Glover Steichen", 2008 (Box 7)
  - Original box description (Box 8)
  - Correspondence and legal documents regarding wills and trusts, 1964-2009; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Correspondence regarding medical treatment and care, 1969-2009 (Box 8)
  - Original box description (Box 9)
  - Photographs, 1933-1955; 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Photograph album, 1933-1936 (Box 9)
  - Photograph album, 1937-1942 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, media, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
  - Photograph albums, 1960-1965; 2 volumes (Box 10)
  - Photograph album, 1947-1948 (Box 11)
  - Card catalog, undated (Box 12)
  - Original box description (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, 1954-2008; 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Tape transcriptions, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Photographs and media, 1947-1959 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence to Aunt Milly, 1915-1922 (Box 13)
  - Financial and legal records, 1977-1984; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Will contest/correspondence, 1973 (Box 13)
  - Animal shelter documents, 1970-1972 (Box 13)
  - Will contest/sculpture sale, 1971-1973 (Box 13)
  - "Lidi", 1977 (Box 13)
  - Publications, 1980 (Box 13)
  - Christmas cards, 1972-1988; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Job applications and resumes, 1959-1969 (Box 13)
  - Photograph albums, 1954-1963; 2 volumes (Box 14)
  - Photograph album, 1944 (Box 15)
  - Original box description (Box 16)
  - Albee correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box 16)
  - Albee articles, 1983-2008 (Box 16)
  - Albee, "Homelife", 2004 (Box 16)
  - Albee, "Me, Myself and I", 2007 (Box 16)
  - Edward Albee Foundation papers, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - "Counting the Ways", 1993 (Box 16)
  - "Marrying Up" media, 1981-1985 (Box 16)
  - "How to Marry Money" media, 1981-1984; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - "Marrying Up" workshops, 1984 (Box 16)
  - "How to Marry Money" book contract and correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - "How to Marry Money" lawsuit, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - "How to Marry Money" script for audio tape and notes, 1982 (Box 16)
  - "How to Marry Money" class notes, undated (Box 16)
  - "Dating Up", undated (Box 16)
  - "Jacqueline Picasso and Me", 1987 (Box 16)
  - "Dreams", 1967 (Box 16)
  - "Peace and Friendship", 1981 (Box 16)
  - "Soul of the Photographer", undated (Box 16)
  - St. Luke's Parish profile, 1997 (Box 16)
  - Joanna's autobiography, undated (Box 16)
  - Family Service League of Support, 1994 (Box 16)
  - Marlboro Music Festival, 1965 (Box 16)
  - Agnes Meyer and Kay Graham media, 1966-1970 (Box 16)
  - Writings, 1981-1996; 4 folders (Box 16)
  - "Ring Around the Collar", undated (Box 16)
  - "Faith and Worship", undated (Box 16)
  - "So, What Else Is New, Mrs....?", 1998 (Box 16)
  - "From Romance to Wisdom", 1996 (Box 16)
  - "Family Story", undated (Box 16)
  - "Living Space", undated (Box 16)
  - "A Giggle of Grandeur", undated (Box 17)
  - "12 Days of Christmas", undated (Box 17)
  - "Who I Am, Who I Was", undated (Box 17)
  - Correspondence, 1944-2008; 7 folders (Box 17)
  - Sandburg correspondence and notes, 1959-1960; 4 folders (Box 17)
  - Wilbur, undated (Box 17)
  - Floor plans, undated; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Info for memoir, undated (Box 17)
  - Original box description (Box 18)
  - Funeral and obituary, 2010 (Box 18)
  - Notes, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Albee correspondence, 1977-2000 (Box 18)
  - Coffee House Club, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Data, chronology, etc., 1967-2010 (Box 18)
  - Writings, 1978-2003 (Box 18)
  - Media, 1975-2000 (Box 18)
  - American Airlines presentation, 1959 (Box 18)
  - Marcou, 2004 (Box 18)
  - "Dating Up", 1985 (Box 18)
  - "Marrying Up", 1984 (Box 18)
  - "Russians", undated (Box 18)
  - Time, undated (Box 18)
  - "Edward Steichen and the Family of Man", 1991 (Box 18)
  - Sebastian Walker, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence, 1967-2008 (Box 18)
  - Floor plans, undated (Box 18)
  - Saturday Review, 1968 (Box 18)
  - "Feminine Eye", 1978 (Box 18)
  - Obituaries, 1982-2008 (Box 18)
  - "In Praise of Older Men", 1967 (Box 18)
  - "In Praise of May-Dec. Brides", 1969 (Box 18)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1968-2003; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Luxembourg exhibit, 1995 (Box 18)
  - Memorabilia, 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - "Living with a Genius", 1971 (Box 18)
  - "Fear-One-Kindness", undated (Box 18)
  - "Jacqueline Picasso and Me", 1987 (Box 18)
  - "On the Other Side of the Camera", 1995 (Box 18)
  - "Edward Steichen, A Memoir", 1988 (Box 18)
  - "A Portrait of WWII" exhibit, undated (Box 18)
  - "Steichen's Eye", 1959 (Box 18)
  - Birmingham Festival of Arts, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Photographs, 1986 (Box 18)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1968-2000 (Box 18)
  - Research, 1963 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence with Francesca, 2000-2009 (Box 18)
  - Meyer file, 1944-1977 (Box 18)
  - "Raging in the Dark", 1995 (Box 18)
  - Photography Center, 1961 (Box 19)
  - MoMA collection, 1997 (Box 19)
  - Luxembourg- Rosch Krieps' book, 1987-2004 (Box 19)
  - "Steichen's Legacy" responses, 2000-2002 (Box 19)
  - Gedrim correspondence, 2000 (Box 19)
  - Reina Sofia, 2007-2008 (Box 19)
  - Slideshow and talk, 2001 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence with parents, 1954-1987 (Box 19)
  - Original box description (Box 20)
  - Psychoanalytic exercise, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence about Bill Meyer, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence from Brendan Gill, 1965-1966 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence from Bill Meyer, 1963-1965 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence from Michael Flanders, undated (Box 20)
  - "Cling, Vine, Cling", undated (Box 20)
  - Correspondence to Bill Meyer, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
  - Notebooks, 1961-1973; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Researchers Take Note (Box 21)
  - "An Ozark Childhood", undated (Box 21)
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 21)
  - Mary Steichen Calderone biography, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Correspondence with Maria, 1982-1985 (Box 21)
  - Stamps, 2001-2004 (Box 21)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1999 (Box 21)
  - Media, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Matisse litigation, 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - Legal documents, 1983-2001 (Box 22)
  - Auction houses, 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Sotheby's, 1990-1993 (Box 22)
  - Matisse: FCS Bond, 1990-1994 (Box 22)
  - Conn. Probate Court, 1988-1992 (Box 22)
  - Larry Freedman, 1988-1994 (Box 22)
  - Zeldes Needle, 1989-1994 (Box 22)
  - Roger Valkenburgh, 1989-1992 (Box 22)
  - Legal expenses, 1989-1991 (Box 22)
  - Kate Steichen's Estate, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Matisse: Litigation, 1973-1990 (Box 22)
  - Matisse: IRS, 1973-1992 (Box 22)
  - Bogus sale, 1989-1990 (Box 22)
  - US District Court, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Polaroid, 1961-1991 (Box 22)
  - Matisse appraisal, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Matisse: Clippings, 1989-1993 (Box 22)
  - MoMA, 1973-1992 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence with MoMA, 1961-1988 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1991 (Box 22)
  - Matisse media and correspondence, 1970-1990 (Box 22)
  - John Paul, 1988-1993 (Box 22)
  - Steichen, Kate: general matters, 1985-1988 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence regarding Kate Steichen's estate, 1988-1990 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence with MoMA, 1988-1989 (Box 23)
  - MoMA documents, 1973-1985 (Box 23)
  - Litigation, 1988-1989 (Box 23)
  - Sale of painting correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 23)
  - MoMA litigation correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Sale of Painting: documents, 1990-1991 (Box 23)
  - Larry Freedman, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Proposal for Sale of Painting, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Mary Steichen Calderone file, 1962-2000 (Box 24)
  - Correspondence to Stieglitz, 1900-1907 (Box 24)
  - "Alienation of Affection" suit, 1919 (Box 24)
  - Pages from Agnes Ernst's diary, 1909 (Box 24)
  - Correspondence, 1902-2000; 3 folders (Box 24)
  - "An Ozark Childhood", undated (Box 24)
  - Correspondence, 1900-1944; 5 folders (Box 24)
  - Original box description (Box 25)
  - "My Trip Abroad", 1926 (Box 25)
  - Russian poems, undated (Box 25)
  - Rodin letter, undated (Box 25)
  - Correspondence with Sandburg, 1939-1961 (Box 25)
  - Sandburg notes, undated (Box 25)
  - Exhibition tag, 1961 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence with Dorothea Lange, 1959-1964 (Box 25)
  - "The Road to Victory", 1942 (Box 25)
  - "Fingal" and "Umpawaug", undated (Box 25)
  - Correspondence with Stieglitz, 1932-1935 (Box 25)
  - Audiovisual Material
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Mary Steichen Calderone oral history, 1986-1987; 30 audiocassettes (Box 26)
      - "1st decade", copy, 1, 1986 August 2; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365455)
      - "2nd decade", copy, 2.1, 1986 August 5; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365463)
      - ends "2nd decade", copy, [1986] August 13; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365745)
      - "3rd decade", 1st part, copy, 2.2, 1986 August 19; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365471)
      - "4th decade", copy, 2, 1986 September 3; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365489)
      - "4th decade", 2nd part, copy, 2.3, 1986 September 17; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365497)
      - "4th decade", end / "5th decade", begin, copy, 3, 1986 September 24; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365505)
      - "6th decade", copy, 4, 1986 December 5; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365513)
      - "personal perp. 2", copy, 5, 1987 March 13; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365521)
      - "personal perp. 2", copy, 6, 1987 March 18; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365539)
      - "personal perp. 3", copy, 7, 1987 March 23; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365547)
      - "personal perp. 3", copy, 8, 1987 April 7; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365554)
      - "personal perp. 4", copy, 9, 1987 April 21; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365562)
      - "personal perp.", copy, 10, 1987 May 12; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365570)
      - [?] "personal perp." / RST, copy, 11, 1987 June 3; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365612)
      - RST, copy, 12, 1987 June 6; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365588)
      - end "personal perp." begins, copy, 13, 1987 June 24; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365596)
      - end "personal perp." begins, copy, 14, 1987 June 25; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365604)
      - copy, 15, 1987 July 15; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365620)
      - S1, copy, 16, 1987 July 1; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365638)
      - S1 / S2, copy, 17, 1987 July 2; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365646)
      - S3, copy, 18, 1987 July 2; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365653)
      - "personal perp. methods democracy" / "personal perp. methods travel", copy, 19, 1987 September 12; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365661)
      - S4, copy, 20, 1987 July 12; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365679)
      - S5, copy, 23, 1987 July 14; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365711)
      - off base, [?] extra, copy, 21, 1987 July 22; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365687)
      - S7, copy, 22, 1987 July 23; 1 (Box 26, Item barcode 39002099365695)